<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.github.SysAdminDoc.StreamKeep</id>
  <name>StreamKeep</name>
  <summary>Download VODs, live streams, podcasts, and direct media URLs</summary>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      StreamKeep is a multi-platform desktop tool for downloading and archiving
      live streams, VODs, podcasts, and direct media URLs. Features native
      extractors for Kick, Twitch, Rumble, SoundCloud, Reddit, Audius, and
      Podcast RSS feeds, with yt-dlp as a universal fallback.
    </p>
    <p>
      Includes channel monitoring with auto-recording, download queue with
      bandwidth scheduling, embedded media player, post-processing (convert,
      trim, silence removal, transcription), upload destinations (S3, FTP,
      WebDAV), and a plugin SDK for community extensions.
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/SysAdminDoc/StreamKeep</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/SysAdminDoc/StreamKeep/issues</url>
  <developer id="com.github.SysAdminDoc">
    <name>SysAdminDoc</name>
  </developer>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.SysAdminDoc.StreamKeep.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="4.36.0" date="2026-07-17">
      <description><p>Adds Podcast Namespace transcript/chapter sidecar downloads, Settings controls for bilingual-subtitle merge and LRC export, and an opt-in YouTube live-chat replay download trigger.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.35.0" date="2026-07-16">
      <description><p>Adds aria2c external-downloader routing with URL sanitization, HAR-capture media/manifest import, an optional queue-complete power action, and a streamkeep:// protocol handler with browser bookmarklet.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.34.0" date="2026-07-16">
      <description><p>Makes HLS parsing and resume standards-complete, corrects WebVTT/podcast transcript parsing, and adds bilingual subtitle merge, LRC export, and YouTube live-chat replay normalization.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.33.0" date="2026-07-16">
      <description><p>Adds a non-DRM HLS clear-key override and hardens backup restore, event hooks, remote image handling, plugin isolation, and credential storage.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.32.0" date="2026-07-16">
      <description><p>Adds full yt-dlp output, subtitle, SponsorBlock, and incremental playlist sync controls.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.31.4" date="2026-06-29">
      <description><p>Adds a restart-persistent failed-job recovery ledger with desktop and web-remote retry/discard actions.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.31.3" date="2026-06-29">
      <description><p>Adds archive integrity manifests and History verify/rescan recovery actions.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.31.2" date="2026-06-01">
      <description><p>Security hardening, extractor fixes, and engineering audit.</p></description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
